work.com 2009-10-27

# Privacy Policy | Work.com

Privacy Policy

Effective October 1, 2006

**INTRODUCTION**

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"), for the Web site located at http://www.work.com (the "Site") made available by Business.com, Inc., the legal owner of the Site, and parent company to Work.com, Inc. ("Work.com", "we", "us" or "our"). This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of certain information relating to your use of the Site. Your use of this Site signifies your understanding and acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Work.com understands and respects your concerns about privacy. We created this Privacy Policy to provide you with notice of what information Work.com may collect, how such information may be used or shared with third parties, and how such information relates to the operation of our Site. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use (the "TCU") posted on the Site, including the provisions regarding change or modification of this Privacy Policy and other policies as set forth in the TCU. 

This Privacy Policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our clients' needs. As we update and diversify our products and services, this Privacy Policy may evolve. Please check this page for updates periodically. We will try to post any changes to this Privacy Policy before they become effective. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here. You are responsible for checking this page periodically for changes and updates to the Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site following any posted changes to the Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of such changes.   
By providing any personal information to this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States and/or any other country. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to exclude your personal information from our direct marketing purposes, please feel free to contact us at [customerservice@work.com](mailto:customerservice@work.com) or by writing to us at Business.com, Attn: Customer Service \- Work.com Privacy, 2120 Colorado Avenue, 3rd Floor, Santa Monica, CA 90404.

The Site is not intended for use by persons under the age of thirteen. Individuals who are under the age of thirteen are expressly prohibited from submitting to Work.com or posting to the Site any personally identifiable information about themselves. 

**This Privacy Policy explains:**

  1. what personally identifiable information Work.com collects from you, and how Work.com uses the information;
  2. with whom your information may be shared;
  3. what choices you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of your information;
  4. what cookies are, and how Work.com uses them;
  5. how Work.com protects your personal information;
  6. how you can access, update or delete your information;
  7. what else you should know about your online privacy; and
  8. how you can contact us.

**1\. What personally identifiable information Work.com collects from you, and how Work.com uses the information.**

Work.com collects and stores personal information in several ways at different parts of our Site. This information may include your legal name, email address, age, gender, address, telephone number(s), areas of indicated interest, financial information, user identification name, user password and other self-identifying information. We collect this information in order to provide you with our services more easily, and in a more personalized manner. We may make message boards and discussion forums available to you. If you choose to voluntarily disclose certain information on any such public area of the Site, this Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. We urge you to exercise caution when disclosing any information on public message boards or discussion forums. 

Work.com also may request certain information using online order forms for products and services. On the order forms, we may collect contact information, financial information, demographic information, method of payment and, if applicable, a credit or debit card number. We may also collect information about you in surveys or for sweepstakes and contests on the Site and information about the searches you perform and the pages you visit on the Site. Work.com may also monitor, on an anonymous aggregate basis, patterns of use in connection with emails that it sends out, including which links are clicked on in our email communications, so that we may use such information to better personalize the content of the Site and our mailings for our users. All such information will be protected in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We may also automatically collect your Internet Protocol address to help diagnose problems and for system administration. Work.com reserves the right to request any additional information necessary to establish and maintain your account for use of the Site. 

Work.com uses the information collected from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Information we collect is used to customize your experience at our Site. We also show you content that we think will be interesting to you, and display content according to the preferences you indicate while on our Site. Work.com may use your information to send you promotional materials about Work.com and its partners. We may also use your information to contact you, if necessary. 

**2\. With whom your information may be shared.**

Work.com will not sell, rent, barter or disclose your personal information other than to its business partners as set forth herein. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "partners" includes, in addition to third parties with whom Work.com may have co-branding or other business relationships or alliances, and Work.com's subsidiaries and other affiliated companies. We encourage our partners to honor their own privacy policies.

We may from time to time aggregate statistical information regarding our customers, traffic patterns and Site usage, or sell our research, which may contain aggregate information. In addition, we may report aggregate information to our advertisers. Such aggregate information will not individually identify any user. 

In order to provide you with co-branded services, and to improve our features, we will sometimes share your information with our partners. We may share your personal information with companies acting as our authorized agents in providing our service or co-branded services (e.g., credit card processing, customer/support services) to you, all of which agree to use it only for such specified purposes. Each partner must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of your information in order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. Because we operate globally, we may transfer your information to countries or jurisdictions that do not provide the same level of data protection as the country in which you are based. If we make such a transfer, we will, or our partners will, as applicable, provide for the proper safeguards required by applicable law to ensure that your information is protected. 

In the event that Work.com is merged, or in the event of a transfer of our assets, Site or operations, Work.com may disclose or transfer your personal information in connection with such transaction. In the event of such a transfer, Work.com will notify you via email or by posting a prominent notice on our Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership of Work.com resulting in a change of control of your personal information. 

We reserve the right to disclose any information if such action is necessary (a) to conform to the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process or subpoena served on Work.com, (b) to protect and defend the legal rights or property of Work.com, the Site, or its users, or (c) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of its users or the general public. We further reserve the right to release any information concerning any user if that user participates (or is reasonably suspected of participating) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution. 

You should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit your personal information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission. 

By providing any personal information to us, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of such personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in, the United States and other countries or territories. Your personal information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal information in the United States may vary and be less stringent than laws of your state or country. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to hold and transmit your personal information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used in this manner please do not register with or use the Site. 

**3\. What choices you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of your information.**

You may occasionally receive information about the products or services you have selected to place on your personal Work.com pages, which may include Work.com products and services, and the products and services of our partners. In the event you are requested to register, you may be given an opportunity to "opt in" to receive mailings from Work.com and/or its partners by "checking" a box in the registration form. If you submit a registration form with the box checked, you thereby consent to being placed on Work.com's mailing list. You may subsequently request to be removed from this list by clicking on the unsubscribe link within a Work.com email or emailing us at [unsubscribe@work.com](mailto:customerservice@work.com). In every update that we send, we may include an option to discontinue receipt of future updates. Work.com reserves the right to limit or reject any registration on our Site to users who do not agree to accept our information or who refuse to provide any information required by Work.com during the registration process.

Regardless of whether or not you elect to receive newsletters or promotional or marketing correspondence from us, such election will not: (a) preclude us from corresponding with you, by email or otherwise, regarding your existing or past relationship with us, and (b) preclude us, including our employees, contractors, agents and other representatives, from accessing and viewing your personal information in the course of maintaining and improving the Site. 

**4\. What cookies are, and how Work.com uses them. **

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, Work.com uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. All portions of the Site that prompt you to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. No other company has access to cookies placed on your computer by Work.com unless you select the option, upon registering with the Site, to share user-information with Work.com's partners. We may use cookies technology to reduce the time required for you to submit your requests and for Work.com to respond to such requests. Cookies will not be used by us to retrieve any information about you, or from your computer, that you have not voluntarily given to us. Cookies may also be placed on your computer when you link from the Site to our partners' Web sites or when you click banner ads provided on our Site. Cookies placed on your computer by third parties by or through the Site, if any, are not within Work.com's immediate control and are not subject to the TCU. If you have any questions concerning third-party cookies, please contact the third party placing such cookies to find out what information is collected and how it is used. WORK.COM ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY THIRD-PARTY COOKIES. 

Please be aware that although you may be able to elect not to accept cookies through certain browser functionality, the features of our Site may not function properly if you do not accept cookies. 

**5\. How Work.com protects your personal information.**

For all our transactions, we employ reasonable Internet security methods and technologies. Where appropriate, we password protect, use encryption techniques and install firewalls. We store your personal information on a secure server, and use procedures designed to protect the personal information we collect from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. 

Although we will take (and require our third-party providers to take) reasonable security precautions regarding your personal information collected from and stored on the Site, because of the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any of your personal information stored on our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access, and we disclaim any liability for any theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks. 

**6\. How you can access, update or delete your information.**

As part of your use of the Site, you are responsible for maintaining and updating, as applicable, your account registration data with current, accurate and complete information. You may view, update and/or edit such registration data that you previously provided to Work.com by logging in to your account and following the appropriate instructions provided therein. 

**7\. What else you should know about your online privacy.**

The Site may also contain links to other Web sites and advertising. The privacy policies of other Web site operators or advertisers may significantly differ from our Privacy Policy. We urge you to contact third party Web site operators or advertisers directly if you have any questions or concerns about their data collection or privacy policies. WORK.COM ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY THIRD-PARTY WEB SITE OPERATORS' OR ADVERTISERS' DATA COLLECTION PRACTICES OR THEIR FAILURE TO ABIDE BY THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES. 

**8\. How you can contact us.**

Any questions about our Privacy Policy should be directed to: 

Business.com  
Attn: Customer Service - Work.com Privacy   
2120 Colorado Avenue, 3rd Floor  
Santa Monica, CA 90404  

© 2009 Business.com, Inc.
